3SL油管接頭卡鉗總泵灌油安裝教學
Helix 3/3.1/3SL/3CARBON Hydraulic Disc Brake Installation Instruction
所需工具
tools
用手把油管螺絲輕輕鎖住
braking oil onto the oil bleeder hole at a torque of 2~3Nm
再使用8mm開口板手將油管鎖付於總泵
Use 8mm adjustable wrench to fasten the connecting bolt on the master cylinder
油管螺絲鎖緊扭力6-8Nm
tighten the hose on to the master cylinder with an 8mm wrench at a torque of 6-8Nm
將注油螺絲於胡琴接頭兩側分別放置O環
Penetrate the Banjo bolt through the Banjo insert with O-ring on each side
將胡琴接頭鎖設於卡鉗
and fasten on the caliper
使用鈕力板手鎖緊鈕力6-8Nm
at a torque of 6-8Nm
M6xP1x18前叉螺絲+華司將符合規格
tighten the qualified adaptor on the front fork or frame by M6XP1X18 adaptor fixing bolt
之轉接座鎖接在前叉或車架上
將轉接座安裝於前叉與車架上即可
將卡鉗安裝於轉接座上,但不要鎖緊
Install the calipers on the adaptor by M6 calipers fixing bolt (2pcs) loosely
但不要鎖緊
and let calipers be able to swivel left and right for adjusting its position.
使卡鉗能夠自由左右調整其位置即完成
END